

To Minh Triet

JUNIOR REACTJS

17/01/2001

**** 0775509168

Ho Chi Minh city

www.linkedin.com/in/tmtriet-work

1 https://tmt-mo.github.io/Portfolio/

INTRODUCTION

I am a Junior React developer with one year of experience, specializing in ReactJS and TypeScript. Recently, I've worked on booking systems and marketplace platforms using Ant Design, NextJs and MobX. I am also skilled in creating responsive and user-friendly UIs with forms and tables, ensuring a positive UX that meets customer requirements. Here is my introduction: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1FHd9TG70PgDH61kzCImbErqu0m_kZ_8/view?usp=sharing

EDUCATION

VAN LANG UNIVERSITY

2018 - 2023

MAJORS IN: SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

- <u>Main subjects:</u> Computer science, OOP, Web application programming, Computer science for practicing engineers, Software architecture and design, Project management, Information system application-Database.
- Grade: 8.29 => GPA: 3.30

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR REACTJS DEVELOPER

10/2023 - 08/2024

BMD SOLUTIONS

- Proficient in React v18, Typescript, Ant Design, MomentJs, Scss, TailwindCss, and other React UI libraries including React-big-calendar and ExcelJs.
- Specialized in developing admin websites for Booking Systems (Spa, Hospital, Hotel), and marketplace platforms. Notable projects include Fclass, Vitadairy, and Joy Bookie, where I gained experience in working with tables, forms, and data display.
- Regularly utilize custom hooks for efficient data handling, along with common hooks such as useState, useRef, useMemo, useCallback, useImperativeHandle, and useEffect.
- Collaborate closely with a leader who is also responsible in Backend to brainstorm ideas and solutions for optimizing module performance and enhancing UI aesthetics.
- Participate in daily meetings with team members to review progress, discuss ongoing tasks, troubleshoot challenges, and devise solutions.
- Frequently engage with clients to gather feedback on software UI/ UX and improvements, ensuring that their needs and concerns are addressed effectively.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

10/2022 - 06/2023

VAN LANG UNIVERSITY - GRADUATE PROJECT

- Working with React v18 and Typescript, TailwindCss, Material UI, RESTful API.
- Creating custom axios requests (handle requests, expire token with interceptor).
- · Managing asynchorous actions and global states with Redux thunk.
- My role was a team leader and a Frontend developer. I lead my team (6 people) and got a pretty high grade as 8.0.
- Come up with plan and schedule suiltable date with customer to discuss what will do next, review the progress and also organizing daily meeting with team mates

INTERNSHIP

INTERNSHIP OF SUPPORTING ON RUNNING TFT SYSTEM

02/2023 - 05/2023

INTERN REACTJS

07/2022 - 10/2022

LOTTE MART HEAD OFFICE - 040 CHANNEL

- Crawling Data from retail competitors (using Nodejs, Puppeteer).
- · Coding marketing mail (Html, CSS, Mailchimp).

CÔNG TY CỔ PHẦN KỶ NGUYÊN SỐ

Using React, Redux Thunk to manage asynchronous actions.

Combine RESTful API and Ant Design to get and put data on UI

SKILLS

- **Programming:** HTML 5, CSS 3, Javascript ES6+, Reactjs 18, Typescript, TailwindCss, Material UI, Redux Thunk, Ant Design, Scss, Styled component, Git, MobX
- · Soft skills: Collaboration, self-taught, problem solve.
- · Others: Be able to use English in such as reading documents of any technologies, framework/ library's APIs
- Languages: English (Intermediate) willing to learn seriously. Here is my introduction: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1FHd9TG70PgDH61kzCImbErqu0m_kZ_8/view?usp=sharing

SALARY EXPECTATION

Expected range is around 12.000.000 VND/month (Net). However, I am open to negotiation and would consider other factors such as benefits, growth opportunities, and the overall compensation package.

KEY STRENGTHS

- Willing to learn new technologies in Web development.
- Be responsible, and be able to work under high pressure.
- Learn to have the self-discipline to adapt to a new environment and new team.

HONORS & AWARDS

TOEIC 670/990

2021-2022

Bachelor's degree (Classification: Good)

2018 - 2023

DESIRES

- · Vision: Become a senior full-stack developer, mastering web applications, within the next 5 years.
- · Network: I aim to build a reputation grounded in honesty and enthusiasm.
- International environment: I'm eager to work in a global company to enhance my English and embrace diverse cultures.